export const quizData = [
  {
    question: 'What does "ㄷ" represent in English?',
    correctAnswer: '"d" as in "dog"',
    options: [
      '"n" as in "no"',
      '"m" as in "man"',
      '"d" as in "dog"',
      '"k" as in "key"',
    ],
  },
  {
    question: 'Which vowel is pronounced as "eo" as in "bus"?',
    correctAnswer: 'ㅓ',
    options: ['ㅓ', 'ㅗ', 'ㅛ', 'ㅏ'],
  },
  {
    question: 'What does "여보세요" mean?',
    correctAnswer: 'Used when starting a phone call.',
    options: [
      'Formal greeting when entering a shop.',
      'Used when starting a phone call.',
      'Polite phrase for hard work.',
      'Greeting among friends.',
    ],
  },
  {
    question: 'What is the Sino-Korean number for 5?',
    correctAnswer: '오 (O)',
    options: ['하나 (Hana)', '오 (O)', '다섯 (Daseot)', '삼 (Sam)'],
  },
  {
    question: 'How do you say "Formal goodbye" to someone staying?',
    correctAnswer: '안녕히 계세요',
    options: ['안녕히 계세요', '안녕히 가세요', '잘 자요', '안녕히 주무세요'],
  },
  {
    question: 'Which color does "노란색" represent?',
    correctAnswer: 'Yellow',
    options: ['Blue', 'Yellow', 'Red', 'Green'],
  },
  {
    question: 'How do you say "Excuse me, where is the restroom?" in Korean?',
    correctAnswer: '이 근처에 화장실이 어디에 있어요?',
    options: [
      '이 근처에 화장실이 어디에 있어요?',
      '이거 얼마예요?',
      '안녕히 계세요.',
      '가장 좋아하는 색깔은 무엇이에요?',
    ],
  },
  {
    question: 'What does "아버지" mean in English?',
    correctAnswer: 'Father',
    options: ['Mother', 'Father', 'Brother', 'Sister'],
  },
  {
    question: 'How do you say "Good night" informally in Korean?',
    correctAnswer: '잘 자요',
    options: ['안녕히 계세요', '잘 자요', '안녕히 주무세요', '안녕히 가세요'],
  },
  {
    question: 'What is the Korean word for "price"?',
    correctAnswer: '가격',
    options: ['가격', '세일', '할인', '더 주세요'],
  },
  {
    question: 'What does "사람 한 명" mean?',
    correctAnswer: 'One person.',
    options: ['One apple.', 'One person.', 'Two people.', 'Three people.'],
  },
  {
    question: 'What is the Korean phrase for "Can I see the menu, please?"',
    correctAnswer: '메뉴 좀 볼 수 있을까요?',
    options: [
      '메뉴 좀 볼 수 있을까요?',
      '이거 얼마예요?',
      '좋은 하루 되세요.',
      '도와주세요!',
    ],
  },
  {
    question: 'How do you say "I want to check in" in Korean?',
    correctAnswer: '체크인하고 싶어요.',
    options: [
      '체크인하고 싶어요.',
      '체크아웃은 몇 시에요?',
      '객실에 와이파이가 있나요?',
      '이거 얼마예요?',
    ],
  },
  {
    question: 'What does "1시" mean in English?',
    correctAnswer: '1 o’clock',
    options: ['1 o’clock', '2 o’clock', '3 o’clock', '10 o’clock'],
  },
  {
    question: 'Which of these is a tense consonant?',
    correctAnswer: 'ㄲ (kk)',
    options: ['ㄱ (g/k)', 'ㄴ (n)', 'ㅂ (b/p)', 'ㄲ (kk)'],
  },
  {
    question: 'How do you say "help me" in Korean?',
    correctAnswer: '도와주세요!',
    options: [
      '도와주세요!',
      '좋은 하루 되세요!',
      '안녕히 계세요!',
      '이 근처에 화장실이 어디에 있어요?',
    ],
  },
];
